

oung

340, Mokdongseo-ro, Yangcheon-gu, Seoul, 08089, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-9686-8177 | **■** tyoung96@yonsei.ac.kr | **☆** taeyoung96.github.io | **回** Taeyoung96

"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."

Summary.

This is Taeyoung Kim, who wants to become an autonomous driving or robotics Perception engineer. My research interests are Computer Vision and SLAM. I like to take on challenging tasks and I like to grow up with my colleagues around me. That's why I record and share what I did on my Github or Technical Blog. I'm also interested in contributing open-source projects.

Research Interests

Computer Vision Object Detection, Segmentation, Depth Estimation, 3D reconstruction

SLAM Visual SLAM, Visual Odometry, Visual Inertial SLAM

Education

Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN VEHICLE CONVERGENCE ENGINEERING (ADVISOR: PROF. EUNTAI KIM)

Mar. 2022 - Feb. 2024 (Expected)

- · Join the mobile robot team
- · Research on visual inertial slam and a study that combines visual slam with deep learning

Kwang Woon University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022

- Total GPA: 4.10 / 4.50, Major GPA: 4.41 / 4.50
- Club: BARAM (Robotics Academic Group) [2020 Staff] , DAISY (English Conversation Club) [2019 Spring President]

Work Experience _____

Computer Vision Lab @Korea Univ

Seoul, S.Korea

Undergraduate Lab Intern (Advisor: Prof. Sangpil Kim)

Mar. 2021 - Jul. 2021

- Research on Computer Vision using an Event camera
- Event data processing using ESIM

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN (ADVISOR: DR. KANGGEON KIM)

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Research on Monocular Depth Estimation
- Participated in KIST disinfect robot (Al Disinfection Robot) project [Video]

Image Process System Lab @Kwang Woon Univ

Seoul, S.Korea

Undergraduate Lab Intern (Advisor: Prof. Donggyu Sim)

May. 2020 - Aug. 2020

- Research on Image Processing based on Deep learning
- Participated in seminars related to Deep Learning and Image Processing

Publication

INTERNATIONAL JOURNAL

Special Issues: Digital Healthcare in Pandemics, Heeju Hong, Wonkook Shin, Jieun Oh, Sunwoo Lee,

Taeyoung Kim, Woosub Lee, Jongsuk Choi, Seungbeum Suh and Kanggeon Kim,

2021.11 "Standard for the Quantification of a Sterilization Effect Using an Artificial Intelligence Disinfection Robot" -

[Paper], [Link]

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE

UR2021 (Work in progress), Taeyoung Kim, Omer Faruk Ince, JongBeom Baek, Jun-Sik Kim, KangGeon Kim, 2021.7

KROS

Sensors

"Dense Monocular SLAM applied Depth Estimation" - [Paper], [Video]

DOMESTIC CONFERENCE

2021.5	KROS2021, TaeHwan Kim, Taeyoung Kim, GiJae Lee, KangGeon Kim,	KRO.	
	"Recognition of disinfection targets and generation of semantic map for disinfection robot" - [Paper]	NRUS	
2020.9	KSPC2020, Naseong Kwon, Taeyoung Kim, Subin Kim, Joohyung Byeon, Jongsuk Lee, Donggyu Sim,		
	"Luma Mapping with Chroma Scaling based on CNN feature map for VVC subjective quality improvement" -	IEIL	
	[Paper]		

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2020.11 Dean's List , for Academic Excellence	KwangWoon Univ.
2020 0 Eth Disco on D treety Vorce Health Datathan 2020	NAVER CLOUD
2020.9 5th Place on B-track , Korea Health Datathon 2020	PLATFORM
2019.10 Dean's List , for Academic Excellence	KwanaWoon Univ.

HONORS

2021-2	National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship ,	Korea Student Aid
2021-1	for the students, those who have been recommended by the university (Full tuition Scholarship)	Foundation
2020-2	National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship ,	Korea Student Aid
2020-1	for the students, those who have been recommended by the university (Full tuition Scholarship)	Foundation
2019-2	Full tuition Scholarship, for Top seat last semester	KwangWoon Univ.

Skills

Programming C++ / C, Python, JAVA, Matlab **Framework** Pytorch, Tensorflow, Keras **DevOps** Git, Docker, ROS2 / ROS **Languages** Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity _____

Technical Blogs Github blog

WRITERS May. 2020 - Present

Ministry of Science and ICT

May. 2021 - Jun.2021

- You can easily access the blog using [this link].
- Writing some posts about lecture summary, paper review, some tips for developments.
- To share what I have studied with others and to remember it longer.

2021 Open Source Contribution Academy

Aug. 2021 - Nov. 2021 MENTEE

- I am in the process of translating a Pytorch tutorial into Korean that I want to contribute to the spread of PyTorch.
- Using Github, I developed the ability to collaborate and contribute to open source.

• The open source repository I've contributed can be found [here].

CLOVA AI RUSH 2021 NAVER AI Lab, NAVER CLOVA

• Only 150 students are allowed to participate in this project.

• I developed my own deep learning model related to multi-label classification.

• I ranked 30th on Project 1-3.

PARTICIPANT

2021 Spring Capstone Design

KwangWoon Univ. Mar. 2021 - Jun.2021

- I made a wireless charging electric vehicle charging robot.
- I designed the control input algorithm, trained deep learning model, and developed the ROS package.
- The source code related to this project is on my [Github repository].

FEBRUARY 6, 2022 TAEYOUNG KIM · CURRICULUM VITAE

Monocular Depth Estimation with ORB-SLAM2

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020 PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

- I was curious about the performance of the recent depth estimation model.
- I used 'Monocular Depth Estimation with Transfer Learning pretrained MobileNetV2' model and applied to ORB-SLAM2 also compared with ORB-SLAM2(Monocular mode), ORB-SLAM2(RGB-D mode)
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].

Runner Alarm System based on Deep Learning

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Apr. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- I wanted to distinguish between walking children and running children with an object detection model.
- When children are running for an amount of time, a beep sounds.
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].